Guide to the Derrick A. Bell, Jr. Papers MC.138
New York University Archives
- ADDITIONAL ACCESSIONS: SERIES IV: COURSE MATERIALS, 1991- 1995
  - Current Constitutional Issues, Student Papers, Fall 1994 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights at the Crossroads: Student Papers, Memos, Class Notes, Fall 1994 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Crosswords Seminar: Student Papers, 1989-1994 (Box 69, Folder 13-21, 23, 25-27)
  - Constitutional Law, Exams, Spring 1992 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Civil Rights at the Crosswords: reflections on student papers, Spring 1992 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Civil Rights at the Crossroads: Grade Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 28-29)
  - Scrapbook, 1961-1972 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276678
  - MacDowell Colony, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Lawyer's Committee for Civil Rights Under Law, 1989-1990 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - La Alianza, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Kenneth Karst, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - HLS Information, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - The Julius Lester Incident, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - "Love Letter" to the Black Man, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Letters-The Final Report, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Law and Technology Committee (HLS), 1988 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Harvard Black Tenured Faculty, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Walter Hooke File, 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - The Randy Kennedy Letter - The Racial Critique, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Houston Grad Fellowship (HLS), 1988-1990 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Korematsu, Hirabayashi, et al, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Charles Hamilton Houston, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Ngongi, Mbella Ikomi, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - LDF, 1988-1990 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Prof. David Kennedy, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - HLS Student Organization, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - National Bar Association, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Bill Hines - Univ. of Iowa, 1987-1989 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Constitutional Law, 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Barcode: 31142042276686
  - Memoranda, circa 1994 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Constitutional Law - Lecture Notes, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Constitutional Law, 1987-1990 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Constitutional Law - Readings (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Constitutional Law - Readings (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Constitutional Law (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Constitutional Law (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Civil Rights at the Crossroads Seminar - Publication Release Forms, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Harvard Law School, 1973-1989 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Harvard Law Record, 1989 September 15 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Memorial Church (Cambridge, MA), ca. 1988 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Article by Howard, Jeff - "Getting Over the River Jordan", circa 1980s (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Inroads, Inc., circa 1990 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Hirabayashi v. United States, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Civil Rights at the Crossroads Seminar - Article by Reich, Charles A., 1988 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Short Stories by Mahony, Rhona, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Harvard Law School Newsletters, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Illinois Committee on Black Concerns in Higher Education, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276694
  - Honda Campus All-Star Challenge, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - St. Lawrence, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Howard University, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Bates College, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - First Presbyterian Church of Brooklyn, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - LaGuardia Community College, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Loyola New Orleans School of Law, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - National Black Leadership Commission on AIDS, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - NYU Law Review Banquet, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - MIT, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Worcester State, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - The Smithsonian African-American Studies Center, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Black Women's Task Force - Phoenix, AZ, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - San Jose State, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Univ. of Alabama at Birmingham, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Rochester Institute of Technology, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Princeton University, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - BALSA Conference NYU, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - NYU BALSA Dinner, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Morehouse College, Benjamin E. Mays Lecture, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Community Church of New York, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Women's City Club of NYC, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Siloam Presbyterian Church, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - DePauw University, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Univ. of Illinois, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Morehouse Candle Award, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Millersville Univ., Pennsylvania, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Univ. of Wisconsin, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Commonwealth, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Univ. of Maryland, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - The Literary Society, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Wright State - Dayton, Ohio, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Valparaiso Law School, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Univ. of Maryland Law School, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Miami Univ. of Ohio, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Univ. of Pennsylvania, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - Judson Memorial Church, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - St. Paul School - Concord, NH, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - Black Human Resource Network, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - Media for 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - Chicago-Book Tour, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - Cambridge/Boston, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 43)
  - Dallas/Atlanta/Florida, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 44)
  - Mortgage and Insurance, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 45)
  - Austin-Williams and Lawrence, 1987-1990 (Box 72, Folder 46)
  - The Black Scholar: Black Popular Movements, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276702
  - NY State Judicial Commission on Minorities, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - HLS Advisor, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous - chronological, 1992-1994 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Various Writings, 1980-1989 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - National Lawyers Guild, MA Chapter dinner honoring DB, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Book Reviews, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - National Criminal Justice Commission, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Black Looks: Race and Representation, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Article re: Jester Hairston, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Chapters, Articles from Various Authors, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Various Writings and Speeches, 1980-1989 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Writings and Articles re: 1990s race issues, 1988-1995 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Course materials, inc. exams RESTRICTED, 1991-1996 (Box 74)
    Barcode: 31142042276710
  - Law Memos and Cases re: School Desegregation, 1960-1969 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276728
  - Law Documents re: School Desegregation, 1960-1961 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - DB's Personal Notes on Civil Rights, 1960-1969 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - NAACP Lyal Defense and Educational Fund, 1960-1969 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Lyal Documents re: Civil Rights, Desegregation, 1960-1969 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Law Documents re: Desegregation, 1960-1969 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Personal Papers re: Health, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276736
  - Bell/Harvard/Race, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1983-1992 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1971-1987 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1980-1987 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1984-1987 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1982-1987 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights at the Crossroads coursepack, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
    Barcode: 31142042276744
  - Constitutional Law Reflections - Hypothetical #1 RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Richard Moot - Task Force and Committees, 1982-1991 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - 1989 Sanford E. Sarasohn Memorial Lecture (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - "And We Are Not Saved" Book Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 77, Folder 7-8)
  - Supreme Court Decision Making Fall 1991 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Summer Address List RESTRICTED, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Constitutional Law Summer Address List RESTRICTED, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Crits - Constitutional Law Study, 1980-1986 (Box 77, Folder 12-13)
  - Religious Freedom Restoration Act, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Constitutional Law, Fall 1995 Hypothetical #3 RESTRICTED (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - LCC Affirmative Action Discussion, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - NY Times Article re: U. of Penn. Gender and Law Studies, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - University Senate Meeting, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Constitutional Law: Assignments of Counsel and Amici Curiae, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Docket/Calendar, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Participatory Grading Memo, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Romer vs. Evans Student Responses RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Con Law Hypothetical #1 Electric Boat v. Horton RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - "A" paper topics Fall 1994 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Con Law Hypothetical #2 Simpson v. United States RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Reflections Hypothetical #2 US v. Simpson RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Con Law Hypothetical #4 Short-Handled Hoe RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Class Reflections US v. Independent Oil RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Class Bios RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Constitutional Law Articles, 1990-1994 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Barcode: 31142042276751
  - Constitutional Law Memos to Students, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Constitutional Law Notes, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Student papers RESTRICTED, 1988-1995 (Box 79)
    Barcode:31142042276769
  - Draft copy of "Faces at the Bottom of the Well" along with book notes and research (Almost empty box), 1955-1992 (Box 80)
    Barcode:31142042276777
  - Hypothetical #29 Reflections RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276785
  - Hypothetical #29 Xenna v. Arcadia RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Hypothetical #28 Reflections RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Hypothetical #28 RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Hypothetical #27 Reflections RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Hypothetical #26 Reflections RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Hypothetical #27 Earp v. Handgun Control RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Hypothetical #25 Reflections RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Hypothetical #25 Hue v. Hilton Med. RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Hypothetical #24 Reflections RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Hypothetical #24 Fresno Bee RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Hypothetical #30 Johnson Valley v. Ima Parent RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Personal Statement RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Minority Women Judges, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Howard/History as Prophecy, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Lessons for Law Reform Lawyers in the Lani Guinier Affair, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Constitutional Law #1 RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Constitutional Law #2 RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, personal, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276793
  - Correspondence, personal, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, general, 1992-1995 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, February, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, March, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, April, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, May, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, June, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, July, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, summer, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, September, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, October, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, November, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, December, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, notes, personal items, 1989/1991 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Articles, newsclippings re: civil rights, discrimination, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276801
  - Articles, newsclippings re: civil rights, discrimination, 1987-1992 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Articles, newsclippings re: civil rights, discrimination, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Articles, newsclippings re: civil rights, discrimination, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Articles re: hate crimes, 1991-1993 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Articles, reviews re: crime, 1990-1993 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Articles, reviews re: discrimination, education, 1986-1993 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Student Papers RESTRICTED, 1991-1995 (Box 84)
    Barcode: 31142042276819
  - Student Papers RESTRICTED, 1992-1994 (Box 85)
    Barcode: 31142042276827
  - NAACP, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276835
  - With Liberty and Justice for All, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - NYU Society of Fellows, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Faces at the Bottom of the Well, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - University of Washington, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Fairfield University, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - The Black Scholar re: Clarence Thomas Hearings, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Ethical Humanist Society, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Fairfield, CT, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Fairfax Dinner, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - SUNY Binghamton, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Community Renewal Society, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Urban League Annual Conference, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - University of Arizona, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Merrill Lynch Reception, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Howard Law School, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Sheila Rush, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Saturday School, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Completed Speeches, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Boule, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - University of Connecticut School of Law, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - University of Texas, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Yale Law Journal, 1990-1991 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - American Ethical Union - Elliott-Black Award, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Greenlining Coalition, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - National Black Wholistic Conference, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Little Rock Conference NAACP, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Women Lawyers Division (NBA), 1991 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Travel Schedule, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Touro Law School, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Toussaint, 1989-1991 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - California Law Review Ms. Paula Chertok, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Urban League, 1990-1991 (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Anderson Publishing Co., 1991 (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - RESTRICTED, 1989-1991 (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - UC Davis Law School Commencement, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - University of Arizona Law School, 1990-1991 (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Northeastern University Commencement, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Publications. Articles, publications, Law Reviews, and newsclippings. Brochures, programs, owners manuals and invoices. One photograph dated 1977., 1959-1992 (Box 87)
    Barcode: 31142042276843
  - Faces at the Bottom of the Well, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276850
  - Writings/Presentations, 1979-1988 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopedia: DeVita, Peter Joseph, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Writings/Presentations, 1982-1993 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - AAAA - 18th Annual National Conference, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Faces at the Bottom of the Well Ch.6, The Rules of Racial Standing, undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Introduction of Faces at the Bottom of the Well: Divining the Permanence of Racism (speech), 1991 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Law School Saturday School Session Racial Realism, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - The William Belden Noble Lectures, "The Difficulty of Doing Good", 1990 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Chicago NAACP Annual Dinner, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Harvard Divinity School Speech, "What Color Was Jesus?", 1991 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights at the Crossroads Seminar Fall 1990 Syllabus (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - ABA Conference on Academic Freedom and Legal Education (Tulane Law School), 1992 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Columbia University Conference on the History and Legacy of the Civil Rights Movement, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Constitutional Issues Seminar Refreshment Reimbursement, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Bridging Communities: A Conversation with Reverend Al Sharpton, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Lawyer-to-Lawyer Network, Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Fall 1992 Speaking Engagements (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Washington Bar Association, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Fifth Annual Law Day Luncheon Atlanta, GA, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Articles, 1979-1991 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276868
  - Articles, 1979-1991 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Articles, 1979-1991 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Course Materials RESTRICTED, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Articles, 1988-1991 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Law Journals, 1983-1991 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Law Information, 1980-1991 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Articles re: D. Dinkins/Giuliani, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276876
  - Harvard News Clippings, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Personal photos, Correspondence, 1980-1988 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Articles re: race, discrimination, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Court cases re: discrimination, 1971-1988 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Articles, correspondence re: Harvard Law School/discrimination, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Articles, correspondence re: civil rights, 1986-1988 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Articles re: Howard Beach, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Newsclippings, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Articles, correspondence, reference materials re: civil rights, 1986-1988 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Academic/law journals re: race/law, 1963-1989 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Articles re: race/racism on campus, 1986-1988 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Law Cases, assorted, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276884
  - Articles, newsclippings, 1987-1991 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Academic journals, 1987-1991 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Newsclippings, articles, 1982-1991 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings, articles, 1987-1991 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Newsclippings, articles, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Articles, newsclippings, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Constitutional Law Exams, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276892
  - Constitutional Law Exams, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Current Constitutional Issues, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Constitutional Law, 1991-1992 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Constitutional Law Exam Questions, 1991-1992 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - NYU Faculty Teaching, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Current Constitutional Issues, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Constitutional Law, 1991-1992 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Constitutional Law, 1991-1992 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Constitutional Law, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Constitutional Law, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Constitutional Law RESTRICTED, 1991-1994 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Court Cases used in Courses, 1990-1996 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276900
  - Court Cases used in Courses, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Constitutional Law Exams, undated (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Current Constitutional Issues Second Reading Packet, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Current Constitutional Issues Handouts, 1988-1991 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Civil Rights at the Crossroads, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Writings, 1976-1977 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276918
  - Writings, 1978-1980 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Writings, 1980-1987 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Writings, 1988-1989 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Writings, 1990-1991 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Writings, undated (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Student Papers RESTRICTED, 1987-1994 (Box 95)
    Barcode: 31142042277031
- ADDITIONAL ACCESSIONS: 99-008 & 00-004
  Not in series order.
  - Toussaint Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276926
  - Black Mutiny, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Wedding Kamina, Aliya, undated (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Third World Press, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Portland, ME, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Annual Luncheon for Wiley A. Branton, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - American Foundation Banquet (St. Louis), 1997 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - St. Alban's Congregational Church, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - American Psychological Association, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Black Caucus - American Association of Librarians, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Thurgood Marshall Summer Law Intern Program, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - NAACP - Pittsburgh, 1996-1997 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Pace Law School Social Justice Center, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - NPA Task Force, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Bethel African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Judge Gabrielle McDonald, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Race and Ethnicity Conference, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Bates College, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - UCLA Thurgood Marshall Lecture Series, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Judson Memorial Church Ordination, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - NYU Convocation, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - New York Lawyers for the Public Interest, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Drug Reform, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Pittsburgh, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - NBA of Columbia Law School, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Teacher's College, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Learning Alliance, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - First Presbyterian Church of Brooklyn, 1995-1997 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Nebraska Law School, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Papyrus Book Store, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - SALT Conference (CUNY Queens), 1997 (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - SALT Dinner, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Emory Black Students, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - SEF Conference (Atlanta), 1997 (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - NYU Black Faculty Literary Week, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - Smith College, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 37)
  - Judson Memorial Church, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 38)
  - Watchung Booksellers, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - LA Times Book Review, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 40)
  - Montclair, NJ, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 41)
  - Hughes Memorial United Methodist Church, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 42)
  - Richard Harris, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 43)
  - The New School, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 44)
  - Stetson Law School, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 45)
  - Howard Thurman Center Daytona/Stetson, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 46)
  - New York Society for Ethical Culture, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 47)
  - United Baptist Tabernacle, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 48)
  - San Francisco City College, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 49)
  - Reed College, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 50)
  - Lane Community College, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 51)
  - Stanford University, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 52)
  - Delaware State University, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Barcode: 31142042276934
  - Berkeley Lecture, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Portland Black United Front, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Eugene, OR, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - University of Tulsa College of Law, "The Burger Court: Counter-Revolution or Confirmation?", 1996 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Oxon Hill Library, Derek McGinty Shaw, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Church of Park Manor, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Learning Alliance Sep. 16, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Black Federal Judges Meeting (Chicago), 1996 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - DeWitt Wallace-Readers Digest, Mildred Hudson, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Radio Interviews (completed), 1996 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Nashville, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Bedford-Stuyvesant Reading, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Speakers Day Program, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Speech File: Atlanta, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 16)